{
    "id": "ab6f596b686545fb8e6b8a328e38f857",
    "title": "Exclamations | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5b2c2ddef0664cf184a59b9c73126091",
            "title": "Exclamations | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "............................... cold it is!",
                    "description": "We use 'how' before an adjective and 'what' before an adjective + noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "How",
                        "What",
                        "Such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................. lovely weather!",
                    "description": "We use 'how' before an adjective and 'what' before an adjective + noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How beautifully ..............................!",
                    "description": "Note the pattern: how + adjective/adverb + subject + verb",
                    "answers": [
                        "dances she",
                        "does she dance",
                        "she dances"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................ pleasant surprise!",
                    "description": "We use 'What a/an' before adjective + singular countable noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How",
                        "What a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "What a beautiful smile ................................!",
                    "description": "In exclamations the subject goes before the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "your daughter has",
                        "has your daughter",
                        "does your sister have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You talk ............................. rubbish!",
                    "description": "'Such' is used before an uncountable noun. 'Such a' is used before a countable noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is .................................. beautiful!",
                    "description": "So is used before an adjective. Such is used before a noun or adjective + noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is .............................. kind woman!",
                    "description": "Use such a before a singular countable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... shameful defeat!",
                    "description": "Use 'what a' before a singular noun or adjective + singular noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "What a",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ............................. clever boy!",
                    "description": "Use 'such a' before adjective + singular countable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. beautiful flowers!",
                    "description": "Use 'what' before adjective + noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ big city Tokyo is!",
                    "description": "We use 'what a' before adjective + singular countable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "What a",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}